{
"question": "学校",
"answer": "がっこう"
},
{
"question": "川",
"answer": "かわ"
},
{
"question": "手",
"answer": "て"
},
{
"question": "戸",
"answer": "と"
},
{
"question": "眼鏡",
"answer": "めがね"
},
{
"question": "煙草",
"answer": "たばこ"
},
{
"question": "赤",
"answer": "あか"
},
{
"question": "仕事",
"answer": "しごと"
},
{
"question": "英語",
"answer": "えいご"
},
{
"question": "問題",
"answer": "もんだい"
},
{
"question": "部屋",
"answer": "へや"
},
{
"question": "子供",
"answer": "こども"
},
{
"question": "時間",
"answer": "じかん"
},
{
"question": "雨",
"answer": "あめ"
},
{
"question": "先生",
"answer": "せんせい"
},
{
"question": "年",
"answer": "とし"
},
{
"question": "手紙",
"answer": "てがみ"
},
{
"question": "電話",
"answer": "でんわ"
},
{
"question": "水",
"answer": "みず"
},
{
"question": "病気",
"answer": "びょうき"
},
